<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Krishi Crew</string>

    <string name="history_origin">
        Agriculture in Jammu and Kashmir has a history as rich and diverse as the region itself. Nestled in the northernmost part of India,
        the states  unique geographical location and climatic conditions have shaped its agriculture over the centuries.
        The practice of farming in this region dates back to ancient times, with historical references to
        Kashmir fertile lands found in texts as old as the Mahabharata and Kalhana Rajatarangini.
    </string>

    <string name="register_now"><u>Register Now</u></string>

    <string name="farmer_about">"KRISHI CREW" is like a helpful friend to farmers in Jammu and Kashmir. offering a range of advantages.
        This online portal provides three main services to make farming easier and more successful.
        First, it helps farmers identify and deal with pests and diseases that can harm their crops,
        ensuring healthier harvests. Second, it predicts how well crops will do in the upcoming season,
        so farmers can plan better and know what to expect, which can save them time and resources.
        It even helps farmers find out what crops are in demand in the market, ensuring they grow the right things.</string>

    <string name="npk_detection_about">
        NPK (Nitrogen, Phosphorus, and Potassium) detection, when combined with environmental factors like rainfall, temperature, pH, and humidity,
        plays a pivotal role in revolutionizing agriculture in Jammu and Kashmir. By assessing soil nutrient levels, farmers can fine-tune fertilizer use,
        promoting healthier crop growth and maximizing yield. This approach aids in crop selection, rotation, and the efficient utilization of resources,
        as NPK data is intrinsically linked with environmental conditions. Additionally, data-driven decision-making, predictive analytics, and
        sustainable practices are made possible, leading to precise yield predictions and contributing to food security, while safeguarding the
        region agricultural sustainability and prosperity
    </string>

    <string name="insurance_policy_about">
        Extending insurance policies to farmers in Jammu and Kashmir is a pivotal measure to safeguard their agricultural endeavors from the inherent
        risks of the region. Tailored insurance schemes can address the unique challenges faced by farmers,
        including unpredictable weather patterns, natural calamities, and crop-specific vulnerabilities.
        These policies encompass weather-based, yield-based, and livestock insurance, as well as coverage for agricultural equipment and infrastructure.
        Furthermore, they can include health insurance for farmers and income protection to shield against income fluctuations.
        Collaborative efforts between the government, insurance providers, and agricultural experts are essential in designing customized insurance
        initiatives that are accessible and financially viable for farmers, especially those in remote areas
    </string>

</resources>